export const questions = [
    {date: "December 1, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 1), day: 1, question: "What is 1 + 1", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 2, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 2), day: 2, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 3, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 3), day: 3, question: "What color is Mars?", answer: "red"},
    {date: "December 4, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 4), day: 4, question: "What is the powerhouse of a cell", answer: "mitochondria"},
    {date: "December 5, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 5), day: 5, question: "What is 27 / 3", answer: 9},
    {date: "December 6, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 6), day: 6, question: "What is the capitol of Texas", answer: "austin"},
    {date: "December 7, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 7), day: 7, question: "How many feet does a cow have?", answer: 4},
    {date: "December 8, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 8), day: 8, question: "What is 54 + 45", answer: 99},
    {date: "December 9, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 9), day: 9, question: "How many states are in the US?", answer: 50},
    {date: "December 10, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 10), day: 10, question: "What year did the US get founded?", answer: 1776},
    {date: "December 11, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 11), day: 11, question: "Who was the 1st President of the US?", answer: "george washington"},
    {date: "December 12, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 12), day: 12, question: "What is the coldest season?", answer: "winter"},
    {date: "December 13, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 13), day: 13, question: "What is the largest mammal alive?", answer: "whale"},
    {date: "December 14, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 14), day: 14, question: "What country is north of the US?", answer: "canada"},
    {date: "December 15, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 15), day: 15, question: "What agency explores space?", answer: "nasa"},
    {date: "December 16, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 16), day: 16, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 17, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 17), day: 17, question: "What is 1 + 1", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 18, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 18), day: 18, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 19, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 19), day: 19, question: "What is 1 + 1", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 20, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 20), day: 20, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 21, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 21), day: 21, question: "What is 1 + 1", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 22, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 22), day: 22, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 23, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 23), day: 23, question: "What is 1 + 1", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 24, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 24), day: 24, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
    {date: "December 25, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 10, 25), day: 25, question: "What is 5 - 4", answer: 1},
]